ethicaljobs.com.au 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy — EthicalJobs.com.au - Community Jobs, Environmental Jobs & Not-For-Profit Jobs

**1\. EthicalJobs.com.au's commitment to maintaining your privacy**

EthicalJobs.com.au's Privacy Statement has been created because we value our users and recognise their right to keep personal information private. This statement discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for all sites managed by EthicalJobs.com.au.

 **2\. Collecting information on EthicalJobs.com.au visitors  
**  
EthicalJobs.com.au collects information on our site visitors collectively including which sections of the site are most frequently visited, how often and for how long. This data is always used as aggregated, non-personal information. EthicalJobs.com.au utilises this information to improve and enhance our services by monitoring the areas on the site which are most popular to you. This aggregated information may be shared with EthicalJobs.com.au partners to provide them with an overview of how visitors use the site. This is done for the purposes of providing you with the best online career management services.

EthicalJobs.com.au uses cookies to provide you with a better experience. These cookies and applets allow you to use specific services such as the Weekly Updates e-newsletter, to remember who you are for Auto Login. Users who do not wish to receive cookies can instruct their web browsers to refuse them. However, doing so will prevent access to some areas of the site and limit your use of some of the EthicalJobs.com.au services.

 **3\. Collecting information on EthicalJobs.com.au's registered Jobseekers**

As part of registering with EthicalJobs.com.au, we collect personal information about you in order for you to take full advantage of our services. To do this it may be necessary for you to provide additional information to EthicalJobs.com.au as detailed below.

Registration  
Registration is completely optional. However, registration allows you to take advantage of more of the tools and resources on the Site, including receiving weekly email updates. Registration includes submitting your name and email address. You may access and modify this information at any time by clicking on the "My Account" link at the top of your screen.

 **4\. Email communications from EthicalJobs.com.au**

EthicalJobs.com.au provides you with selected information about job seeking and career-related topics in our email newsletter. This free service is sent to registered users and provides the option of opting out of receiving these by changing clicking the "unsubscribe" link in the email. EthicalJobs.com.au may also make you aware of additional products and services which form part of your relationship with us.

 **5\. Storage & Security of Personal Information**

EthicalJobs.com.au takes all reasonable steps to ensure the security of our system. EthicalJobs.com.au allows you to access your information at any time to keep it accurate and up to date. Any information which we hold for you is stored on secure servers that are protected in controlled facilities.

In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by EthicalJobs.com.au. However, EthicalJobs.com.au will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access of your personal information.

You can also play an important role in keeping your personal information secure, by maintaining the confidentiality of any password and accounts used on the EthicalJobs.com.au site. Please notify us immediately if there is any unauthorised use of your account by any other Internet user or any other breach of security.

 **6\. Access to Your Information**

As indicated in point 2, unless you become a registered user, EthicalJobs.com.au does not collect information that identifies you personally. If however, you become a registered user, you are able to change and update your registered profile at any time. Should you require assistance with updating your account or removing your details from the site, this can be requested by email. You can also request your personal information directly from Advertisers who you have applied to on the site.

 **7\. EthicalJobs.com.au Partners & Advertisers**

EthicalJobs.com.au provides links and passes online application to third party sites. The use of your information by these third party sites is not within the control of EthicalJobs.com.au and we cannot accept responsibility for the conduct of these companies. Advertisers who place job ads on EthicalJobs.com.au are asked to comply with Australian federal privacy policy with regard to their own information handling practices.

You may also directly contact advertisers to request access to any personal information that you have sent as part of an application.

 **8\. Feedback**

EthicalJobs.com.au welcomes ideas and feedback about all aspects of the site. EthicalJobs.com.au stores feedback that users send to us. This feedback will be used to administer and refine the service and may be shared with EthicalJobs.com.au partners either in aggregate form or with specific identifying characteristics removed.

 **9\. Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with EthicalJobs.com.au, you can contact us via the details on the [About Us](http://www.ethicaljobs.com.au/about "About Us") page.
